<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru">
  <channel>
    <title>Ynki</title>
    <link>https://ynki.website/</link>
    <description>Full-cycle expert development — from idea and architecture to launch and long-term support. Provide transparent hourly rates, clear milestones, and measurable results. Trusted for our strong community reputation and reliable collaboration, we’ve been delivering high-quality digital products across diverse industries since 2018.</description>
    <language>ru</language>

    <item turbo="true">
      <title>Ynki - Leading Development</title>
      <link>https://ynki.website/en</link>
      <turbo:source>https://ynki.website/en</turbo:source>
      <turbo:topic>Ynki - Leading Development</turbo:topic>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 10:31:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <turbo:content><![CDATA[
      <header>
        <h1>Ynki - Leading Development</h1>
        <p>Full-cycle expert development — from idea and architecture to launch and long-term support. Provide transparent hourly rates, clear milestones, and measurable results. Trusted for our strong community reputation and reliable collaboration, we’ve been delivering high-quality digital products across diverse industries since 2018.</p>
      </header>
      <section>
        <h2>Service catalog</h2>
        <ul><li><strong>Web Development</strong><p>Fast, scalable marketing sites, customer portals and internal dashboards.</p></li><li><strong>Automation &amp; AI Solutions</strong><p>Jobs, bots and ML-powered workflows that remove repetitive manual work.</p></li><li><strong>Backend / API Development</strong><p>Robust APIs, integrations and data layers that power products reliably.</p></li><li><strong>UI/UX Design</strong><p>Research-driven product design, prototyping and usability refinements.</p></li><li><strong>App Development</strong><p>Native and cross-platform apps that keep users engaged on mobile or desktop.</p></li></ul>
      </section>
      <section>
        <h2>Ynki FAQ</h2>
        <details><summary>What projects do you take on?</summary><p>We focus on internal tools, automation layers, admin panels, and SaaS products that support operational work and scale without pain.</p></details><details><summary>How do you share progress?</summary><p>We provide access to repositories, dashboards, time tracking, and regular updates, so progress is always transparent.</p></details><details><summary>When can we start?</summary><p>Discovery, planning and kickoff typically begin within a week. Share the key project context through the consultation form and we help scope the next steps.</p></details><details><summary>What experience do you have?</summary><p>We have launched various licensed digital products with large user audiences. We have supported projects such as "Prometheus" "Starcheat" "Velocity" "Shell-Store."</p></details><details><summary>How can we be sure you are reliable?</summary><p>We are open and transparent in our development process. We have a reputation on various forums and are willing to work through escrow or guarantee systems from the user.</p></details>
      </section>
      <section>
        <h2>How Ynki delivers software projects</h2>
        <ol><li><strong>Engineering first</strong><p>Direct collaboration with the developer who architects, builds, and launches each project for transparent decision-making.</p></li><li><strong>Small steps, visible progress</strong><p>Ship in tight, reviewable milestones with real demos instead of long invisible phases.</p></li><li><strong>Transparent by default</strong><p>Provide access to repositories, dashboards, time tracking, and health metrics so stakeholders never guess about progress.</p></li><li><strong>Focused delivery</strong><p>Keep priorities lean to ship predictable releases that keep roadmaps realistic and dependable.</p></li></ol>
      </section>
  ]]></turbo:content>
    </item>
  

    <item turbo="true">
      <title>Ynki — Ведущая Разработка</title>
      <link>https://ynki.website/ru</link>
      <turbo:source>https://ynki.website/ru</turbo:source>
      <turbo:topic>Ynki — Ведущая Разработка</turbo:topic>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 10:31:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <turbo:content><![CDATA[
      <header>
        <h1>Ynki — Ведущая Разработка</h1>
        <p>Полный цикл экспертной разработки — от идеи и архитектуры до запуска и долгосрочной поддержки. Работаем с прозрачными ставками, понятными этапами и измеримыми результатами. С 2018 года создаём цифровые продукты для разных отраслей и подтверждаем репутацию надёжных партнёров.</p>
      </header>
      <section>
        <h2>Каталог услуг</h2>
        <ul><li><strong>Веб-разработка</strong><p>Быстрые и масштабируемые сайты, клиентские порталы и внутренние дашборды.</p></li><li><strong>Автоматизация и AI</strong><p>Джобы, боты и ML‑процессы, которые убирают рутину и сокращают операционные затраты.</p></li><li><strong>Backend / API</strong><p>Надёжные API, интеграции и дата‑слои, которые становятся фундаментом продукта.</p></li><li><strong>UI/UX дизайн</strong><p>Продуктовый дизайн, исследование пользовательского опыта и прототипирование.</p></li><li><strong>Мобильные и десктоп приложения</strong><p>Нативные и кроссплатформенные продукты, удерживающие пользователей на любых устройствах.</p></li></ul>
      </section>
      <section>
        <h2>Частые вопросы Ynki</h2>
        <details><summary>Какие проекты вы берёте?</summary><p>Фокусируемся на внутренних инструментах, слоях автоматизации, админ-панелях и SaaS‑продуктах, которые поддерживают операционную работу и масштабируются без боли.</p></details><details><summary>Как вы делитесь прогрессом?</summary><p>Предоставляем доступ к репозиториям, дашбордам, учёту времени и регулярным апдейтам, поэтому прогресс всегда прозрачен.</p></details><details><summary>Когда можно стартовать?</summary><p>Исследование, планирование и запуск обычно начинаются в течение недели. Поделитесь техническим заданием через форму консультации.</p></details><details><summary>Какой опыт у вас?</summary><p>Запускали различные цифровые продукты с лицензией которые имели большую аудиторию пользователей. Поддерживали такие проекты как "Prometheus" "Starcheat" "Velocity" "Shell-Store".</p></details><details><summary>Как убедиться, что вы надежны?</summary><p>Открыты и прозрачны в области разработки. Имеем репутацию на различных форумах готовые работать через холд или гарант систему от пользователя.</p></details>
      </section>
      <section>
        <h2>Как Ynki ведёт проекты</h2>
        <ol><li><strong>Инженерия в первую очередь</strong><p>Никаких продавцов и посредников. Вы общаетесь напрямую с разработчиком, который проектирует, пишет и запускает ваш продукт.</p></li><li><strong>Небольшие шаги и демо</strong><p>Предпочитаем небольшие поставки с реальными демо вместо огромных невидимых этапов.</p></li><li><strong>Прозрачность по умолчанию</strong><p>Доступ к репозиториям, админкам, трекингу времени и статусу проекта без дополнительных запросов.</p></li><li><strong>Сфокусированная поставка</strong><p>Держим приоритеты узкими и выпускаем предсказуемые, надежные релизы — чтобы вам было удобно планировать рост.</p></li><li><strong>Как убедиться, что вы надежны?</strong><p>Открыты и прозрачны в области разработки. Имеем репутацию на различных форумах готовые работать через холд или гарант систему от пользователя.</p></li></ol>
      </section>
  ]]></turbo:content>
    </item>
  
  </channel>
</rss>
